stylight.com 2018-12-27

# privacy-policy-en_US - About Stylight

The following privacy notice is valid for the online offer at [www.stylight.com](http://www.stylight.com/).

## Summary - Data protection

Personal data protection is a matter of trust and your trust is highly important to us. It is our interest to respect your privacy and your right to deal with the information about you. In the following, we would like to inform you about our data collection and our use of the data so that you feel safe when using our online offer. The legal rules about dealing with personal data are strictly followed by us.

## Controller

Controller is Stylight Inc, 1900 Market Street, 8th Floor, PA 19103 Philadelphia, info@stylight.com , +49 89 1222 895 - 0, in the following referred to as “we” or “us”.

Exceptions will be explained in this privacy notice.

## 1\. Collection and Processing of Personal Data

### 1.1. General

All information which is related to an identified or identifiable natural person (e.g., name, address, phone number, date of birth or email address) is personal data.

In general, you are able to use our online offer without providing personal data. The usage of certain services may, however, require you to provide personal data, e.g., registration or the participation in a raffle. Mandatory fields are generally denoted accordingly.

### 1.2. Purposes of Processing and Legal Basis for the Processing

We process your personal data for the following purposes, based on the Legal Bases listed:

  * Providing this online offer and performance of contract following our Terms of Use (Legal basis: Performance of a contract).
  * Personalization of the offer (Legal basis: Performance of a contract)
  * Dispatch of a newsletter with the recipient´s consent via email. (Legal basis: Performance of a contract).
  * Performance of raffles under respective raffle terms. (Legal basis: Performance of a contract).
  * House and third party advertising to the legally allowed extent or based on consent. (Legal basis: legitimate interests; there is a legitimate interest in direkt marketing as long as marketing occurs while complying with data protection and fair trade laws).
  * In case you wish to use services which first require the formation of a contract, we will ask you to register. Within the scope of registering, we collect personal data necessary for the formation and performance of the contract (especially e-mail address). Further data can be entered on a voluntary basis.
  * Prevention and protection against misuse (especially bot detection).

## 2\. Data Transfer to Third Parties, Service Providers

### 2.1. Data Transfer to Third Parties

Your personal data is generally only being transferred to third parties as far as this is necessary for performance of the contract, if we or the third party have legitimate interests in transferring or if you have consented to this. If data is transferred to third parties based on legitimate interests, this will be explained in this privacy notice. Beyond or in addition to this, data may be transferred to third parties as far as we are obligated to do so under statutory provisions or an enforceable decision made by an authority or a court.

### 2.2. Data Transfer to Service Providers

We reserve the right to use service providers in collecting or processing data. Service providers are only given personal data that is necessary for their concrete task. This means that your email address may be forwarded to a service provider so you can receive a newsletter that you ordered. Service providers may also be assigned to provide server capacity. Service providers are generally involved as so-called processors which may only process users' personal data based on our instructions.

### 2.3. Data Transfer to Non-EEA Countries

We also forward personal data to third parties or processors who are located outside EEA countries. In such cases we ensure prior to the transfer that the transfer is subject to appropriate safeguards (e.g., by self-certification of the recipient for the [EU US Privacy Shield](https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome) or by having agreed upon so-called standard data protection clauses of the European Union with the recipient) or sufficient user consent is given. You may receive an overview of third country recipients and a copy of the appropriate or suitable safeguards in place. Please use the details provided in the Contact section.

## 3\. Duration of Storage; Retention Periods

We store your data as long as it is necessary to provide our online offer and the services connected with it or as long as we have a legitimate interest in continued storage. In all other cases, we delete your personal data with the exception of such data that we are required to retain for the purpose of contractual or statutory (e.g., taxation or commercial law) retention periods (e.g., invoices). At this point, contractual retention periods may also result from contracts with third parties (e.g., those holding copyrights or IP rights). Data that is only retained because it is subject to a retention period is restricted from processing until the period expires and will then be deleted.

## 4\. Log Files

Every time you use the internet, your internet browser or terminal device automatically transmits certain information which is then saved by us in log files.

We save log files for the purposes of determining disruptions, for security reasons (e.g., to elucidate attack attempts) and for the bot detection for a period of 7 to 30 days and delete them thereafter. Log files which need to remain stored for evidence purposes are excluded from deletion until the respective incident has been finally resolved and may be forwarded to investigating authorities on a case-by-case basis.

Log files contain especially following information:

  * IP address (internet protocol address) of the terminal device which is used to access the online offer;
  * Internet address of the website from which the online offer is accessed (so-called URL of origin or referrer URL);
  * Name of the service provider through which access to the online offer occurs;
  * Name of accessed file or information;
  * Data and time and duration of access;
  * Amount of data transmitted;
  * Operating system and informations on the internet browser used, including add-ons installed (e.g., for the Flash Player) or for the used terminal device;
  * http status code (e.g. “request successful” or “file not found”);
  * Request IDs;
  * Java Session IDs.

Log files are moreover used for app analysis.

## 5\. Cookies

### 5.1. What are Cookies?

Cookies are little text files that are sent when visiting an internet page and are stored in a user’s browser. In case the respective internet page is accessed once again, the user’s browser sends back the content of the cookies and, thus, allows for the recognition of the user. Certain cookies are automatically deleted upon ending the browser session (so-called session cookies), others are saved for a set time or permanently in the user’s browser and delete themselves thereafter (so-called temporary or persistent cookies).

### 5.2. Which Files are Saved in the Cookies?

Cookies generally do not contain personal data, but instead only an online ID.

### 5.3. How can you Avoid the Usage of Cookies or Delete Cookies?

You can deactivate the storage of cookies through your browser settings and you may delete cookies that have already been saved in your browser at any time (see following technical explanations). Please take note that this online offer might not be functional without cookies or the functionality might be reduced.

Please be further advised that refusing to allow the creation of usage profiles partially works through „opt out cookies“. In case you delete all cookies, an objection might, under certain circumstances, no longer be considered or be valid and would have to be restated.

_Technical explanations to delete cookies:_

Internet Explorer:

[support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies#](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies#)

Mozilla Firefox:

[support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences)

Google Chrome:

Safari:

### 5.4. What Cookies do we use?

#### 5.4.1. Cookies Strictly Necessary for a Service

Some cookies are strictly necessary so we can host our online offer safely. This category includes, e.g.,

  * Cookies which serve the purpose of identifying or authenticating our users;
  * Cookies that temporarily store certain user entries
  * Cookies that remember certain user preferences

#### 5.4.2. Analytics Cookies

We use analytics cookies to record and statistically evaluate our users’ usage behavior (e.g., clicked ad banners, visited subpages, search queries asked).

#### 5.4.3. Third Party Advertising Cookies

We also allow other companies to gather data from our users using advertising cookies. This allows us and third parties to show interest-based advertisements to the users of our online offer, which are based on an analysis of their usage behavior e.g., clicked ad banners, visited subpages, search queries) in general and not restricted to our online offer.

#### 5.4.4. Third Party Social Plugin Sharing Cookies in Connection with Social Plugins

Embedding Social Plugins generally has the plugins’ providers store cookies.

## 6\. Web Analysis

We need statistical information about the usage of our Online Offers to design them to be user-friendlier. For this purpose, we use the web analysis tools described in this section. The usage profiles created by these tools using analysis cookies or by evaluating log files are not combined with personal data.

The providers of the tools (vendors) process data only as processors subject to our directives and not for their own purposes. The tools either do not use user IP addresses at all or shorten them immediately after obtaining them. You will find information on each tool's vendor and how you are able to object to the collection and processing of data that is done with the tool. Be advised that with regard to tools that use opt out cookies, the opt out function is related to a device or browser and is thus valid for the terminal device or browser used at this time. In case you use several terminal devices or browsers you must opt out on every device and in every browser used. Additionally, you can generally avoid the creation of usage profiles by generally deactivating cookie usage.

### 6.1. Google Analytics

Google Analytics is provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google"). We use Google Analytics with the additional function offered by Google to anonymize IP addresses. While doing so, Google already shortens IPs within the EU in most cases and only does so in the United States in exceptional cases, while always saving shortened IPs only.

You may object to the collection or processing of your data by using the following link to download and install a browser plugin:[ tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).

### 6.2. SZM Reach Measurement (INFOnline)

SZM Reach Measurement is provided by INFOnline GmbH, Brühler Straße 9, 53119 Bonn, Germany.

You may object to the collection or processing of your data by clicking the following link to download and save an opt out cookie: [optout.ioam.de/](https://optout.ioam.de/).

We are a member of the registered Advertising Media Circulation Determination Information Association (“[IVW](http://www.ivw.eu/englische-version)”) and participate in the “internet facts” study performed by the registered Online Research Consortium ("[AGOF](https://www.agof.de/?lang=en)"). For this reason, the usage statistics created with SZM Reach Measurement are published monthly by AGOF and the Consortium on Media Analysis ("ag.ma") as well as by IVW and can be viewed online with these organizations.

Find further data protection related information [here](https://www.infonline.de/download/infonline-datenschutzerklaerung/?wpdmdl=3591).

Please note that the links in this section are online available in German. If you have any questions, please contact us.

### 6.3. TrackJS

TrackJS is provided by TrackJS LLC, 215 Pine Street West, Stillwater, MN 55082, USA. The setting “Ignore IP” is activated for our account so that TrackJS does not process personal data.

### 6.4. New Relic

New Relic is provided by New Relic Inc., 188 Spear Street, Suite 1200, San Francisco, CA 94105, USA. New Relic does not process personal data.

### 6.5. Weather Data

We are using the services IPstack and Weather API to track location-based weather data. IPstack is provided by apilayer GmbH, Hörlgasse 12/4, 1090 Vienna, Austria. Find further information on this tool [here](https://ipstack.com/). Weather API is provided by Zoomash Ltd, Advantage Business Center, 132-134 Great Ancoats Street, Manchester, M4 6DE, UK. Find further information on this tool [here](https://developer.worldweatheronline.com/).

You may object to the collection or processing of your data by these tools by following our [instructions](http://www.stylight.co.uk/User/Settings/WeatherTracking/).

## 7\. Logging and Evaluating Usage Behavior for Interest Based Advertisement (also for Third Parties)

We want to present to our users advertisements, which are tailored to their interests or special offers (“interest based advertisement”), and want to limit the frequency of the visibility of certain advertisements - limit how often they see certain advertisements. For this purpose, we use the following tools.

The usage profiles created by the tools using advertising cookies or third party advertising cookies, so-called web beacons (invisible graphics which are also called pixels or counting pixels), advertising identifiers or similar technologies. Usage profiles are not combined with personal data.

The tools are used by the providers to show our users in our online offer and in third party offers interest-based advertisements and to steer the frequency with which users see certain advertisements. Regarding the processing of data in connection with the tools, the providers serve as controllers as long as we have not stated otherwise. The tools’ providers forward information, for the purposes mentioned before, to third parties, if necessary.

The tools either do not process user IP addresses at all or shorten them immediately upon collection.

You can find information on a tool's provider for each tool as well as information on how to object to the data collection performed by this tool.

Be advised that with regard to tools which use opt out cookies, the opt out function is related to a device or browser and is thus valid for the terminal device or browser used at this time. In case you use several terminal devices or browsers you must opt out on every device and in every browser used.

Additionally, you are able to generally avoid the creation of usage profiles by generally deactivating cookie usage.  
Further information on interest-based advertising may be found on the consumer portal[ www.meine-cookies.org](http://www.meine-cookies.org/). The following link to the portal also enables you to view the activation status of certain tools provided by different providers and to object to the collection and processing of your data by these tools:[ www.meine-cookies.org/cookies_verwalten/praeferenzmanager-beta.html](http://www.meine-cookies.org/cookies_verwalten/praeferenzmanager-beta.html).

Please note that the links in this section are online available in German. If you have any questions, please contact us.

A key possibility to object to certain tools in particular those issued by U.S.-based providers can be found at the following link:[ optout.networkadvertising.org/#/](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#/)

### 7.1. The ADEX

The ADEX is offered by The ADEX GmbH, Rotherstrasse 22, 10245 Berlin, Germany. This provider processes data only as a processor following our directives and not for its own purposes. Find more information on this tool [here](http://www.theadex.com/#privacy).

You may object to the collection or processing of your data through this tool by downloading and saving the opt out cookie available under this[ link](http://www.theadex.com/opt-out).

### 7.2. Google AdSense

Google AdSense is offered by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google"). Find further information on this tool [here](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/140382?hl=en).

You may object to the collection and processing of your data by this tool by following Google's [user references](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/7395996?hl=en).

### 7.3. Google Doubleclick

Google Doubleclick is offered by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google"). Find further information on this tool [here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads?hl=en).

You may object to the collection and processing of your data by this tool by following Google's[ user references](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/7395996?hl=en).

### 7.4. Criteo Dynamic Retargeting

Criteo is provided by Criteo CIL, 32 Rue Blanche, 75009 Paris, France. Find further information on this tool [here](https://www.criteo.com/privacy/).

You may object to the collection or processing of your data by this tool by following Criteo’s [instructions](https://www.criteo.com/privacy/).

### 7.5. Efficient Frontier (Adobe)

Efficient Frontier (Adobe) is provided by Adobe Systems Software Ireland LTD, 4-6 Riverwalk, City West Business Campus, Saggart, Dublin 24, Ireland. Find further information on this tool [here](https://www.adobe.com/privacy/policy.html).

You may object to the collection or processing of your data by this tool by following Adobe’s [instructions](https://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html).

### 7.6. RTB House

RTB House is provided by RTB House S.A., 61/101 Złota Str., Warsaw (00-819), Poland. Find further information on this tool [here](https://www.rtbhouse.com/privacy/).

You may object to the collection or processing of your data by this tool by following RTB House’s [instructions](https://www.rtbhouse.com/optout-page/).

### 7.7. Affilinet

Affilinet is provided by affilinet GmbH, Sapporobogen 6-8, 80637 München, Germany. Find further information on this tool [here](https://www.affili.net/uk/about-affilinet/data-privacy-compliance).

You may object to the collection or processing of your data by this tool by clicking on the following link and deselect the tracking:  

### 7.8. Facebook

Facebook is provided by Facebook Ireland Limited, 4 Grand Canal Square, Dublin 2, Ireland. Find further information on this tool [here](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation).

You may object to the collection or processing of your data by this tool by clicking on the following link and deselect the tracking: [www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices)

### 7.9. Google Conversions (AdWords)

Google Conversions is provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. Find further information on this tool [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en).

You may object to the collection or processing of your data by this tool by clicking on the following link to download and save the opt-out cookie: [support.google.com/ads/answer/7395996?hl=en](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/7395996?hl=en)

### 7.10. Google Remarketing

Google Remarketing is provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. Find further information on this tool [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en).

You may object to the collection or processing of your data by this tool by clicking on the following link to download and save the opt-out cookie: [support.google.com/ads/answer/7395996?hl=en](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/7395996?hl=en)

### 7.11. Next Performance

Next Performance is provided by Nextperformance SAS, 25 Rue Choiseul, 75002 Paris, Frankreich. Find further information on this tool [here](http://www.nextperf.com/privacy/).

You may object to the collection or processing of your data by this tool by following Next Performance’s [instructions](http://www.nextperf.com/privacy/).

### 7.12. Taboola

Taboola is provided by Taboola Inc. 1115 Broadway, 7th fl., New York, NY, 10010, USA. Find further information on this tool [here](https://www.taboola.com/privacy-policy).

You may object to the collection or processing of your data by this tool by clicking on the following link and deselect the tracking: [www.taboola.com/privacy-policy#optout](https://www.taboola.com/privacy-policy#optout)/

### 7.13. United Internet

United Internet is provided by United Internet AG, Eigendorfer Straße 57, 56410 Montabaur, Germany. Find further information on this tool [here](https://www.united-internet-media.de/en/data-privacy-guidelines/).

You may object to the collection or processing of your data by this tool by clicking on the following link and deselect the tracking: [www.united-internet-media.de/en/services/opt-inopt-out/confirmopt-out/](https://www.united-internet-media.de/en/services/opt-inopt-out/confirmopt-out/)

### 7.14. Google Doubleclick Floodlight Counter

Google Doubleclick Floodlight Counter is provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google"). Find further information on this tool [here](https://support.google.com/tagmanager/answer/6107168?hl=en).

You may object to the collection or processing of your data by this tool by clicking on the following link to download and save the opt-out cookie: [support.google.com/ads/answer/7395996?hl=en](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/7395996?hl=en)

### **7.15. nugg.ad**

nugg.ad is provided by nugg.ad GmbH, Tamara-Danz-Str. 1, 10243 Berlin. Find further information on this tool [here](https://www.nugg.ad/en/privacy/general-information-greece.html).

You may object to the collection or processing of your data by this tool by clicking on the following link to download and save the opt-out cookie: [https://www.nugg.ad/en/privacy/general-information-greece.html](https://www.nugg.ad/en/privacy/general-information-greece.html)

## 8\. Push Notifications

### 8.1. Braze (formerly Appboy)

Braze is provided by Braze Inc., 318 West 39th Street, 5th Floor New York, NY 10018, USA. Find further information on this tool [here](https://www.braze.com/privacy/).

Before sending the push notifications we obtained your approval. It is also possible to object the sending of web push notifications afterwards. Find an explanation [here](https://www.pcworld.com/article/3099172/software/how-to-turn-off-web-notifications-in-chrome-edge-and-firefox.html).

## 9\. Social Plugins

This online offer uses social plugins (“Plugins”) by the following providers:

### 9.1. Facebook

Facebook is operated under www.facebook.com by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA, and under www.facebook.de by Facebook Ireland Limited, Hanover Reach, 5-7 Hanover Quay, Dublin 2, Ireland ("Facebook"). Find an overview of Facebook's plugins and their appearance here: [developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins](http://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins); find information on data protection at Facebook here:[ www.facebook.com/policy.php](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php).

### 9.2. Twitter

Twitter is operated by Twitter Inc., 1355 Market St, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA ("Twitter"). Find an overview of Twitter's plugins and their appearance here: [dev.twitter.com/web/overview](https://dev.twitter.com/web/overview); find information on data protection at Twitter here: [twitter.com/privacy](https://twitter.com/privacy).

### 9.3. Pinterest

Pinterest is operated by Pinterest Inc., 808 Brennan St, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA ("Pinterest"). Find an overview of Pinterest's plugins and their appearance here: [developers.pinterest.com/tools/widget-builder/](https://developers.pinterest.com/tools/widget-builder/); find information on data protection at Pinterest here: [about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy](https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy).

### 9.4. WhatsApp

WhatsApp is operated by WhatsApp Ireland Limited, 4 Grand Canal Square, Grand Canal Harbour, Dublin 2, Ireland (“WhatsApp”). Find information on data protection at WhatsApp here: [www.whatsapp.com/legal/#privacy-policy-how-we-use-information](https://www.whatsapp.com/legal/#privacy-policy-how-we-use-information).

### 9.5. Social Plugins with 2-Click-Solution

The different providers of plugins are in the following summarized as “Plugin Providers”.

To increase the protection of your data when visiting our online offer, plugins are embedded using the so-called "Shariff Solution". This means that when a page of this online offer is accessed, a connection to the servers of the respective plugin provider is not yet established.

Your internet browser establishes a direct connection to the respective plugin provider’s servers only when you activate the plugins. This way, the plugin provider receives information that your internet browser has accessed the respective site of our online offer, even when you do not maintain a user account with the provider or are not logged in. _Log files_ (including the IP address) are transmitted directly from your internet browser to a server of the respective plugin provider and may be stored there. This server may be located outside the EU or EEA (e.g. in the U.S.).

The plugins are stand alone extensions of the plugin providers. We, thus, do not have influence on the scope of data gathered and stored by the plugin provider through the plugin.

If you do not wish for the plugin providers to receive, save, and use data gathered through this online offer, you should not use the respective plugins.

You can also block the plugins from being loaded with browser add ons (so-called script blockers).

Find out more about the purpose and scope of the data collection as well as about processing and use of your data by plugin providers and about your rights and possibilities to change settings to protect your data in the privacy statements of the respective providers.

## 10\. Social Sign In (Login via Social Networks)

### 10.1. Registration/Login via Facebook

We give you the opportunity to register or login with us through your Facebook account. If you do this, we receive the data necessary for registration or signing on (e.g., email address, name) from Facebook.

We are unable to influence the scope of data collected by Facebook through Facebook Login. If you do not wish for Facebook to gather data in connection with your usage of our online offer in order to use it for its own purposes, you should not use Facebook Login.

Find out more about the purpose and scope of the collection as well as about the processing and use of your data by Facebook and about your rights and possibilities to change settings to protect your data in Facebook’s privacy statement:[ www.facebook.com/policy.php](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php).

### 10.2. Login via Google+

We give you the opportunity to register or login with us through your Google+ account. If you do this, we receive the data necessary for registration or signing on (e.g., email address, name) from Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google") (e.g., email address, name).

We are unable to influence the scope of data collected by Google through Google+ Login. If you do not wish for Google to gather data in connection with your usage of our online offer in order to use it for its own purposes, you should not use Google+ Login.

Find out more about the purpose and scope of the data collection as well as about the processing and use of your data by Google and about your rights and possibilities to change settings to protect your data in Google’s privacy statement:[ www.google.com/intl/de/+/policy/+1button.html](http://www.google.com/intl/de/+/policy/+1button.html).

## 11\. Newsletter with Registration; Right of Revocation

We give you the possibility to subscribe to a newsletter. You can withdraw your respective consent at any time. To do so, please use the unsubscribe link located at the end of each newsletter or contact us via the information provided in the Contact section.

## 12\. Users’ rights (Rights of the data subject)

You have the right to receive information as well as – under certain prerequisites – the rights to correction, deletion, restriction of processing or objection to personal data processing and – from May 25, 2018, on – the right to data portability.

Right to object against direct marketing:  
Additionally, you may at all times object to the processing of your personal data for advertising purposes ("advertisement objection"). Please take into account that, due to logistical reasons, there might be an overlap between your objection and the usage of your data within the scope of a campaign which is already running.

In case you receive advertising via push notification, you may also use the deregistration option in the settings of your mobile device to object to advertising (see section Technical Notes)

Objection to data processing ensuing from the legal basis “justified interest”:  
You have the right to object at any time to the processing of your personal data ensuing from the legal basis of justified interest. We will then no longer process your personal data unless we substantiate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your rights.

In case you consented to the processing of your data, you can always revoke this consent at any time. The lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal remains unaffected.

Alternatively, you may use the settings in your user account to correct data stated at your registration or to declare your objection to direct marketing.

You may also delete your user account yourself by clicking on the “Delete Account” button in the Login menu bar.

Please be advised that your data will be initially restricted from processing only if obligatory retention periods do not allow us to delete the data immediately.

## 13\. Right to Complain with the Regulatory Authority

As an European citizen, you have the right to file a complaint with a data protection authority. You can appeal to the data protection authority, which is competent for your place of residence or your state or to the data protection authority which is competent for us. This is:

Bayerisches Landesamt für Datenschutzaufsicht (BayLDA)  
Promenade 27  
91522 Ansbach  
Germany  

## 14\. Contact

We and our data protection officer are available for your inquiries and suggestions regarding data protection at the e-mail address [info@stylight.com](mailto:info@stylight.com) or at [Stefan.Friedrich@prosiebensat1.com](mailto:Stefan.Friedrich@prosiebensat1.com) (data protection officer).

If you want to contact us, you can reach us as follows:

Stylight Inc  
1900 Market Street  
8th Floor  
PA 19103 Philadelphia  
Tel.: +49 89 1222 895 - 0  
Fax: +49 89 1222 895 - 48  

The following privacy notice supplements the privacy notice for the online offer at [www.stylight.com](http://www.stylight.com/) for the usage of mobile applications [Stylight] (“App” or “Online offer”).

## Controller

Controller is Stylight Inc, 1900 Market Street, 8th Floor, PA 19103 Philadelphia, info@stylight.com , +49 89 1222 895 - 0 in the following referred to as [“PROVIDER” or “we” or “us”].

Exceptions will be explained in this privacy notice.

## 1\. Push Notifications

You may receive push notifications from us, also when you are not currently using the app. Such messages may be messages that we send to you within the scope of fulfillment of contract (e.g. in case of suspension of service for maintenance purposes) but also advertising information. You shall only receive advertising information if you explicitly consented to this.

You may deactivate the notifications in the settings of the app at any time. Besides that, you can prevent the receipt of personalized advertisements in the system settings of your mobile device.

_Technical explanation to deactivate personalized advertisements:_

Android operating system:

-> settings -> Google -> display and “reset Advertising ID“ and/or “deactivate customized advertising”

IOS operating system (Apple):

-> setting -> data privacy -> advertising: “reset Ad-ID” and/or “no ad tracking”

## 2\. Data processing by app stores

Before you can install this app, you may have to enter into a user agreement with the respective provider (e.g. Google, Apple) of the app store regulating your access to that portal (e.g. Google Play, Apple Store). The app store provider in this context will collect and process data in connection with the use of the app store such as the user name, e-mail address and individual mobile equipment identity. We are no party to the user agreement with the app store provider and have no influence on its data processing. In this respect, the privacy statement of the respective provider shall apply.

## 3\. App Analysis

We need statistical information about the usage of our Online Offers to design them to be user-friendlier and to perform reach measurements and market research. For this purpose, we use the analysis tools described in this section. The usage profiles created by these tools by evaluating log files are not combined with personal data. The providers of the tools (vendors) process data only as processors subject to our directives and not for their own purposes. The tools either do not use user IP addresses at all or shorten them immediately after obtaining them. You will find information on each tool's vendor and how you are able to object to the collection and processing of data that is done with the tool.

### 3.1. Adjust

Adjust is provided by Adjust GmbH, Saarbrücker Str. 37A, 10405 Berlin, Germany.

### 3.2. Braze

Braze is provided by Braze Inc., 318 West 39th Street, 5th Floor New York, NY 10018, USA.

### 3.3. Sentry

Sentry is provided by Functional Software Inc. 132 Hawthorne St, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA.

## 4\. Advertising Identifier, Advertising ID

We use what is referred to as advertising identifiers, which are provided by the operating system of your mobile device for advertising purposes. In devices using the Android operating system that is the Advertising ID, in devices using the iOS operating system that is the Advertising Identifier (IDFA). Advertising Identifier – as the online identification typically stored in cookies – constitute unique identifications that are not permanently retained, though. The usage profiles generated with these advertising identifiers (e.g. advertising banners that were clicked on, searches) are used to show you advertising that is tailored to your interest (Interest-based Advertising). The data collected for this purpose is not linked to other information concerning your device.

## 5\. How can you prevent or limit the use of Advertising Identifiers?

You may limit the use of advertising identifiers for advertising purpose in the settings of your mobile device or delete the advertising identifier (when you delete it, a new advertising identifier is generated that is not linked to the data collected by the previous identifier).

_Technical explanation to deactivate personalized advertisements:_

Android operating system:

-> settings -> Google -> display and “reset Advertising ID“ and/or “deactivate customized advertising”

IOS operating system (Apple):

-> setting -> data privacy -> advertising: “reset Ad-ID” and/or “no ad tracking”

## 6\. Share functions

Your mobile device allows you to share content from the app with third parties (e.g. via e-mail, SMS or via the share functionalities of social media). We have no influence on the associated processing of data e.g. by social network providers. The respective third party providers are solely responsible in this regard.

## 7\. Data deletion

You may delete any data we collected in connection with this app by simply deleting the app from your mobile device. Please note that your data is first only restricted from processing in case deletion is not admissible subject to retention periods.
